
import { Question, QuestionType } from "./types";

export const QUIZ_DATA: Question[] = [
  // --- NHÓM 1 (CÂU 1-20) ---
  { id: 1, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There aren’t any _ _ _ _ _ at all in the village where we used to live.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_42.mp3", correctAnswer: "buses", explanation: "Buses: Xe buýt." },
  { id: 2, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "People are open, plain and _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_35.mp3", correctAnswer: "frank", explanation: "Frank: Thẳng thắn." },
  { id: 3, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Would you like to p_ _ _ _ a portrait of me?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s1.mp3", correctAnswer: "aint", explanation: "Paint: Vẽ." },
  { id: 4, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Some el_ _ _ _ nts live in the mountains.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s8.mp3", correctAnswer: "epha", explanation: "Elephants: Những con voi." },
  { id: 5, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "My father uses YouTube to watch _ _ _ _ _ _ _ shows.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s6.mp3", correctAnswer: "cooking", explanation: "Cooking: Nấu ăn." },
  { id: 6, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "We are surrounded by green _ _ _ _ _ _ , flowers and trees.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_34.mp3", correctAnswer: "fields", explanation: "Fields: Cánh đồng." },
  { id: 7, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Lang Son province has 12 education centers offering _ _ _ _ _ _ language classes, mostly Tay and Nung.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_43.mp3", correctAnswer: "ethnic", explanation: "Ethnic: Dân tộc." },
  { id: 8, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The man's watch is ________.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_23.mp3", options: ["in the kitchen", "in the washing machine", "on the bed", "on the bath"], correctAnswer: "on the bath", explanation: "Đồng hồ ở trên bồn tắm." },
  { id: 9, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I'm enjoying a peaceful _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ a lot more than the busy city life.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_21.mp3", correctAnswer: "lifestyle", explanation: "Lifestyle: Phong cách sống." },
  { id: 10, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Please _ _ _ _ off the fans when you go out.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s14.mp3", correctAnswer: "turn", explanation: "Turn off: Tắt đi." },
  { id: 11, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "A festival adds structure to our social lives and connects us with our families and _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_92.mp3", correctAnswer: "backgrounds", explanation: "Backgrounds: Nền tảng xã hội." },
  { id: 12, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "My first lesson this morning was _ _ _ , and our teacher talked to us about Pablo Picasso.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s21.mp3", correctAnswer: "Art", explanation: "Art: Mỹ thuật." },
  { id: 13, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "If we're going the right way, we'll drive past the _ _ _ _ _ station soon.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s26.mp3", correctAnswer: "train", explanation: "Train station: Ga tàu." },
  { id: 14, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "He's good at bu_ _ _ _ _ _ things.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s24.mp3", correctAnswer: "ilding", explanation: "Building: Xây dựng." },
  { id: 15, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The La Chi ethnic people in Nam Khanh commune have upheld a lot of traditional culture and production, including growing cotton and _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_108.mp3", correctAnswer: "weaving", explanation: "Weaving: Dệt vải." },
  { id: 16, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "It was t_ _ _ _ _ degrees yesterday so it was much too hot inside.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s27.mp3", correctAnswer: "hirty", explanation: "Thirty degrees: 30 độ." },
  { id: 17, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "My parents will be at home the night I want my _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s25.mp3", correctAnswer: "party", explanation: "Party: Bữa tiệc." },
  { id: 18, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "One of the biggest problems we face is _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_106.mp3", correctAnswer: "garbage", explanation: "Garbage: Rác thải." },
  { id: 19, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "How many pandas were born?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_120.mp3", options: ["six", "twenty", "two", "twice"], correctAnswer: "two", explanation: "Có 2 con gấu trúc được sinh ra." },
  { id: 20, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The River Thames in London was one of the worst-_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ rivers in the study.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_59.mp3", correctAnswer: "affected", explanation: "Affected: Bị ảnh hưởng." },

  // --- NHÓM 2 (CÂU 21-40) ---
  { id: 21, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "She likes _ _ _ _ _ _ sports such as swimming and hiking.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_18.mp3", correctAnswer: "summer", explanation: "Summer: Mùa hè." },
  { id: 22, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Parents and children can spend time enjoying the same hobby and build a closer r_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_16.mp3", correctAnswer: "elationship", explanation: "Relationship: Mối quan hệ." },
  { id: 23, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "At the age of 80 he still remembers by heart several stories about the old Then m_ _ _ _ _ _ _ of the Tay.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_51.mp3", correctAnswer: "elodies", explanation: "Melodies: Giai điệu." },
  { id: 24, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Students learn reading and listening through topics and traditional _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and customs.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_44.mp3", correctAnswer: "culture", explanation: "Culture: Văn hóa." },
  { id: 25, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Lucy seldom has lunch at _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s11.mp3", correctAnswer: "home", explanation: "Home: Nhà." },
  { id: 26, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "People in my village are really _ _ _ _ -hearted.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s4.mp3", correctAnswer: "kind", explanation: "Kind-hearted: Tốt bụng." },
  { id: 27, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "They have a _ _ _ _ cultural life with a number of age-old festivals and customs.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_48.mp3", correctAnswer: "rich", explanation: "Rich: Giàu/Phong phú." },
  { id: 28, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The man can't teach his classes because his _ _ _ _ is bad again.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_6.mp3", correctAnswer: "back", explanation: "Back: Cái lưng." },
  { id: 29, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Before New Year’s day, people go shopping for food and drinks, repair the house or put up _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_88.mp3", correctAnswer: "decor", explanation: "Decor: Trang trí." },
  { id: 30, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Village life is free from all rest_ _ _ _ _ _ of society.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_65.mp3", correctAnswer: "raints", explanation: "Restraints: Ràng buộc." },
  { id: 31, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I can't come. It's my _ _ _ _ _ _ 's birthday.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s23.mp3", correctAnswer: "sister", explanation: "Sister: Chị/Em gái." },
  { id: 32, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "What do people do to _ _ _ _ _ _ _ for the festival?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_87.mp3", correctAnswer: "prepare", explanation: "Prepare: Chuẩn bị." },
  { id: 33, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "We regularly organize field trips for students to _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ with ethnic people to better understand their culture, customs, and habits.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_69.mp3", correctAnswer: "communicate", explanation: "Communicate: Giao tiếp." },
  { id: 34, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "If there's a problem, I'm called from my of_ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s23.mp3", correctAnswer: "fice", explanation: "Office: Văn phòng." },
  { id: 35, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "New Year’s day is a chance for family _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and parties.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_84.mp3", correctAnswer: "reunion", explanation: "Reunion: Sum họp gia đình." },
  { id: 36, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "What does Lara do in her free time?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_112.mp3", options: ["cooking", "gardening", "painting", "both B and C"], correctAnswer: "both B and C", explanation: "Thích cả làm vườn và vẽ." },
  { id: 37, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The stonecutter wishes he would be a ____.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_118.mp3", options: ["poor servant", "rich man", "powerful king", "prince"], correctAnswer: "prince", explanation: "Prince: Hoàng tử." },
  { id: 38, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Bonfire Night is celebrated on _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ 5.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_52.mp3", correctAnswer: "november", explanation: "Tháng 11." },
  { id: 39, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I grew up in the country in a very small farm and it was kind of _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_22.mp3", correctAnswer: "boring", explanation: "Boring: Nhàm chán." },
  { id: 40, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Lan usually buys food in the super_ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s11.mp3", correctAnswer: "market", explanation: "Supermarket: Siêu thị." },

  // --- NHÓM 3 (CÂU 41-60) ---
  { id: 41, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ oes and pigs live on the farm.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s8.mp3", correctAnswer: "Buffal", explanation: "Buffaloes: Những con trâu." },
  { id: 42, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Stamp collecting can help build _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ s between people from around the world.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_15.mp3", correctAnswer: "friendship", explanation: "Friendship: Tình bạn." },
  { id: 43, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "It is interesting to learn about the people and things that are pictured on the _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_14.mp3", correctAnswer: "stamps", explanation: "Stamps: Những con tem." },
  { id: 44, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The band uses his dad's _ _ _ _ _ _ because his bedroom's too small.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_11.mp3", correctAnswer: "garage", explanation: "Garage: Nhà để xe." },
  { id: 45, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "People in my village are really hospi_ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s4.mp3", correctAnswer: "table", explanation: "Hospitable: Hiếu khách." },
  { id: 46, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The city is much more _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and a lot more to do and see and experience.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_23.mp3", correctAnswer: "exciting", explanation: "Exciting: Thú vị." },
  { id: 47, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Mrs. Bright made us wear special gl_ _ _ _ _ so that we wouldn't hurt our eyes.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s22.mp3", correctAnswer: "asses", explanation: "Glasses: Những chiếc kính." },
  { id: 48, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I have heard the weather will be _ _ _ _ _ these days.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s20.mp3", correctAnswer: "sunny", explanation: "Sunny: Có nắng." },
  { id: 49, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Do you have a nice co_ _ _ _ _ as you're the star of the show?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s24.mp3", correctAnswer: "stume", explanation: "Costume: Trang phục." },
  { id: 50, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I don't have to show my passport or my driving _ _ _ _ nce, do I?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_54.mp3", correctAnswer: "lice", explanation: "Licence: Giấy phép." },
  { id: 51, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Being able to _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and use ethnic languages in daily life is very useful for their work.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_70.mp3", correctAnswer: "understand", explanation: "Understand: Hiểu biết." },
  { id: 52, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The New Year’s day is celebrated all over the _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_86.mp3", correctAnswer: "country", explanation: "Country: Đất nước." },
  { id: 53, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The rock, paper, scissors world championship was first held in ____.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_111.mp3", options: ["1394", "1934", "1945", "1954"], correctAnswer: "1934", explanation: "Held in 1934." },
  { id: 54, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ s say the worst-hit rivers are in western Europe and North America.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_56.mp3", correctAnswer: "researcher", explanation: "Researchers: Những nhà nghiên cứu." },
  { id: 55, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Would you like to l_ _ _ me your chessboard?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s1.mp3", correctAnswer: "end", explanation: "Lend: Cho mượn." },
  { id: 56, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "You should _ _ _ _ _ your mouth when you cough or sneeze.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_58.mp3", correctAnswer: "cover", explanation: "Cover: Che đậy." },
  { id: 57, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The river smelled bad because of all sorts of _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and waste in the water.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_105.mp3", correctAnswer: "chemicals", explanation: "Chemicals: Hóa chất." },
  { id: 58, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The stonecutter and his wife didn’t have much _ _ _ _ _ , but they were happy together.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_98.mp3", correctAnswer: "money", explanation: "Money: Tiền." },
  { id: 59, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "On New Year's Eve, people have a party with _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ food and drinks.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_90.mp3", correctAnswer: "traditional", explanation: "Traditional: Truyền thống." },
  { id: 60, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "It'll be really _ _ _ _ _ as we're going as a group.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s20.mp3", correctAnswer: "cheap", explanation: "Cheap: Rẻ." },

  // --- NHÓM 4 (CÂU 61-80) ---
  { id: 61, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "He'd like to buy a kum_ _ _ _ tree.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s9.mp3", correctAnswer: "quat", explanation: "Kumquat tree: Cây quất." },
  { id: 62, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Live_ _ _ _ _ are the animals we keep on a farm.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s7.mp3", correctAnswer: "stock", explanation: "Livestock: Gia súc." },
  { id: 63, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "You can feel completely _ _ _ _ in the countryside.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_28.mp3", correctAnswer: "safe", explanation: "Safe: An toàn." },
  { id: 64, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "In the country, we are close to _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_33.mp3", correctAnswer: "nature", explanation: "Nature: Thiên nhiên." },
  { id: 65, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "What _ _ _ _ _ l media does Taylor use?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s5.mp3", correctAnswer: "socia", explanation: "Social media: Mạng xã hội." },
  { id: 66, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I got everything I remembered. Milk, bread, veg_ _ _ _ _ _ _ , and the newspaper.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s26.mp3", correctAnswer: "etables", explanation: "Vegetables: Rau củ." },
  { id: 67, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The river smelled bad because of all sorts of _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and waste in the water.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_105.mp3", correctAnswer: "chemicals", explanation: "Hóa chất." },
  { id: 68, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Scientists say that a new kind of robot can re_ _ _ _ _ _ _ - it can create baby robots.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_45.mp3", correctAnswer: "produce", explanation: "Reproduce: Tái sản xuất." },
  { id: 69, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "He added that rivers in many rich nations are unrecognisable _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ with how they were 200 years ago.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_58.mp3", correctAnswer: "compared", explanation: "Compared: So với." },
  { id: 70, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "What is their new meeting time?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s29.mp3", options: ["9 a.m.", "12 a.m.", "1 p.m.", "11 a.m."], correctAnswer: "9 a.m.", explanation: "Thời gian gặp mới là 9h sáng." },
  { id: 71, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There aren’t any _ _ _ _ _ at all in the village where we used to live.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_42.mp3", correctAnswer: "buses", explanation: "Xe buýt." },
  { id: 72, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "He'd like to buy a kum_ _ _ _ tree.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s9.mp3", correctAnswer: "quat", explanation: "Cây quất." },
  { id: 73, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Live_ _ _ _ _ are the animals we keep on a farm.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s7.mp3", correctAnswer: "stock", explanation: "Livestock: Gia súc." },
  { id: 74, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "You can feel completely _ _ _ _ in the countryside.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_28.mp3", correctAnswer: "safe", explanation: "Safe: An toàn." },
  { id: 75, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I don’t mind spending my free time alone _ _ _ _ _ _ _ or surfing the Internet.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_8.mp3", correctAnswer: "reading", explanation: "Reading: Đọc sách." },
  { id: 76, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "In the country, we are close to _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_33.mp3", correctAnswer: "nature", explanation: "Nature: Thiên nhiên." },
  { id: 77, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "What _ _ _ _ _ l media does Taylor use?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s5.mp3", correctAnswer: "socia", explanation: "Social: Mạng xã hội." },
  { id: 78, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Some el_ _ _ _ nts live in the mountains.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s8.mp3", correctAnswer: "epha", explanation: "Elephants: Những con voi." },
  { id: 79, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Would you like to l_ _ _ me your chessboard?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s1.mp3", correctAnswer: "end", explanation: "Lend: Cho mượn." },
  { id: 80, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "You should _ _ _ _ _ your mouth when you cough or sneeze.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_58.mp3", correctAnswer: "cover", explanation: "Cover: Che đậy." },

  // --- NHÓM 5 (CÂU 81-100) ---
  { id: 81, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The city is much more _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and a lot more to do and see and experience.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_23.mp3", correctAnswer: "exciting", explanation: "Thú vị, hào hứng." },
  { id: 82, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The man's watch is ________.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_23.mp3", options: ["in the kitchen", "in the washing machine", "on the bath", "on the bed"], correctAnswer: "on the bath", explanation: "Trên bồn tắm." },
  { id: 83, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There’s so much _ _ _ _ _ _ _ here these days.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_24.mp3", correctAnswer: "traffic", explanation: "Giao thông." },
  { id: 84, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The preservation and promotion of Then singing is a major _ _ _ _ _ _ _ of Then artists.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_50.mp3", correctAnswer: "concern", explanation: "Mối quan tâm." },
  { id: 85, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "My parents go j_ _ _ _ _ _ in the park almost every morning.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s2.mp3", correctAnswer: "ogging", explanation: "Jogging: Chạy bộ." },
  { id: 86, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "This city is so _ _ _ _ _ _ at night.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_27.mp3", correctAnswer: "boring", explanation: "Boring: Nhàm chán." },
  { id: 87, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "We can pick up _ _ _ _ er in the playground after school.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s13.mp3", correctAnswer: "litt", explanation: "Litter: Rác." },
  { id: 88, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The _ _ _ _ _ _ _ show begins at 2.15 every afternoon.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_13.mp3", correctAnswer: "dolphin", explanation: "Dolphin: Cá heo." },
  { id: 89, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "My uncle uses Google Drive to save _ _ _ _ _ _ es.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis4s6.mp3", correctAnswer: "pictur", explanation: "Pictures: Những bức tranh." },
  { id: 90, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "She doesn't like the _ _ _ _ in the city.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_26.mp3", correctAnswer: "mall", explanation: "Mall: Trung tâm thương mại." },
  { id: 91, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The girl has _ _ _ _ _ lessons until late every Friday.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s16.mp3", correctAnswer: "dance", explanation: "Dance: Nhảy múa." },
  { id: 92, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "She's going to _ _ _ _ a song.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s24.mp3", correctAnswer: "sing", explanation: "Sing: Hát." },
  { id: 93, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The lucky winner will win a three-night stay, for two people, in the wonderful _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ countryside.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop8/nghe/E8_Quan2022_41.mp3", correctAnswer: "Scottish", explanation: "Scottish: Vùng Scotland." },
  { id: 94, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The promotion of ethnic minorities has contributed to _ _ _ _ _ _ _ fying tourism products.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_76.mp3", correctAnswer: "diversi", explanation: "Diversifying: Đa dạng hóa." },
  { id: 95, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The things people do on the first day will bring good luck and _ _ _ _ _ _ rity to them.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_91.mp3", correctAnswer: "prospe", explanation: "Prosperity: Sự thịnh vượng." },
  { id: 96, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I'm going to wear my _ _ _ _ s.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis2s18.mp3", correctAnswer: "jean", explanation: "Jeans: Quần bò." },
  { id: 97, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I got everything I remembered. Milk, bread, veg_ _ _ _ _ _ _ , and the newspaper.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis1s26.mp3", correctAnswer: "etables", explanation: "Vegetables: Rau củ." },
  { id: 98, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "I know she likes to _ _ _ _ _ flowers.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE2023-2024/Chinhthuc/Capquan/Lop8/Audio/CQ8Lis3s18.mp3", correctAnswer: "plant", explanation: "Plant: Trồng." },
  { id: 99, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The rock, paper, scissors world championship was first held in ____.", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_111.mp3", options: ["1945", "1394", "1954", "1934"], correctAnswer: "1934", explanation: "Năm 1934." },
  { id: 100, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "How many Tay and Nung language classes were held?", audioUrl: "https://cdn-s3.vtconline.vn/ioe-resource-02/filePublish/ioe/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop8/amthanh/k8-caphuyen-nghe_116.mp3", options: ["8000", "2015", "over 200", "under 100"], correctAnswer: "over 200", explanation: "Trên 200 lớp." }
];
